Guide to the Reginald Moore Sugar Land Convict Leasing System research collection, 1878-2018 MS 636
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XI: Addendum of materials released after the death of Reginald Moore
  - Photographs taken by Reginald Moore and Bill Martin, Archaeologist, Texas Historical Commission, while touring the Central Prison Unit grounds, Sugar Land, Texas., 2016 (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
    The prison was closed in 2011, and most buildings were razed in 2018.
  - Archaeological Study of Proposed 75- Acre Joseph S. and Lucie H. Cullinan Park, Fort Bend County, Texas, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    The area covered in this report was part of former prison grounds in the Sugar Land, Texas region.
  - Intensive Mechanically Augmented Survey and Construction Monitoring of the 21-Acre Ace Center Music Hall, City of Sugar Land, Fort Bend County, Texas, by Goshawk Environmental Consulting, for City of Sugar Land, 2015-04 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Lead agency: Texas Historical Commission. Authors: Ron Ralph and Reign Clark. Area includes Smart Financial Arena and UH Sugar Land.
  - Intensively mechanically Augmented Archaeological Survey of the 163 Acre Central State Prison Farm Tract, Sugar Land, Texas, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Photocopied research articles on slavery and convict leasing in Texas (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Note fragments by Reginald Moore (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Photos of Reginald Moore touring Museum of African American Culture and Heritage, Smithsonian, 2019-05
  - Reginald Moore funeral service video